<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='update site: http://junginger.biz/eclipse/' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1520800274227'/>
    <property name='site.checksum' value='2457554963'/>
  </properties>
  <references size='2'>
    <repository uri='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/' url='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/' type='0' options='0'/>
    <repository uri='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/' url='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/' type='1' options='0'/>
  </references>
  <units size='15'>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.5.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' range='[0.0.0,1.5.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.5.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.5.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.5.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.5.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' version='1.3.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' range='[0.0.0,1.3.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' version='1.3.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' version='1.3.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' version='1.3.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' version='1.5.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.5.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='RssViewFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='RSS View newsfeed reader with a compact UI for Eclipse 3.2+.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' version='1.5.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='4'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.2.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' range='[1.5.0,1.5.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' range='[1.5.0,1.5.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html' url='http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html'>
          GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE&#xA;                       Version 3, 29 June 2007&#xA;&#xA; Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. &lt;http://&#xA; fsf.org/&gt; Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute&#xA; verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it&#xA; is not allowed.&#xA;&#xA;                            Preamble&#xA;&#xA;  The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft&#xA;  license for software and other kinds of works.&#xA;&#xA;  The licenses for most software and other practical works&#xA;  are designed to take away your freedom to share and&#xA;  change the works.  By contrast, the GNU General Public&#xA;  License is intended to guarantee your freedom to share&#xA;  and change all versions of a program--to make sure it&#xA;  remains free software for all its users.  We, the Free&#xA;  Software Foundation, use the GNU General Public License&#xA;  for most of our software; it applies also to any other&#xA;  work released this way by its authors.  You can apply it&#xA;  to your programs, too.&#xA;&#xA;  When we speak of free software, we are referring to&#xA;  freedom, not price.  Our General Public Licenses are&#xA;  designed to make sure that you have the freedom to&#xA;  distribute copies of free software (and charge for them&#xA;  if you wish), that you receive source code or can get it&#xA;  if you want it, that you can change the software or use&#xA;  pieces of it in new free programs, and that you know you&#xA;  can do these things.&#xA;&#xA;  To protect your rights, we need to prevent others from&#xA;  denying you these rights or asking you to surrender the&#xA;  rights.  Therefore, you have certain responsibilities if&#xA;  you distribute copies of the software, or if you modify&#xA;  it: responsibilities to respect the freedom of others.&#xA;&#xA;  For example, if you distribute copies of such a program,&#xA;  whether gratis or for a fee, you must pass on to the&#xA;  recipients the same freedoms that you received.  You must&#xA;  make sure that they, too, receive or can get the source&#xA;  code.  And you must show them these terms so they know&#xA;  their rights.&#xA;&#xA;  Developers that use the GNU GPL protect your rights with&#xA;  two steps: (1) assert copyright on the software, and (2)&#xA;  offer you this License giving you legal permission to&#xA;  copy, distribute and/or modify it.&#xA;&#xA;  For the developers&apos; and authors&apos; protection, the GPL&#xA;  clearly explains that there is no warranty for this free&#xA;  software.  For both users&apos; and authors&apos; sake, the GPL&#xA;  requires that modified versions be marked as changed, so&#xA;  that their problems will not be attributed erroneously to&#xA;  authors of previous versions.&#xA;&#xA;  Some devices are designed to deny users access to install&#xA;  or run modified versions of the software inside them,&#xA;  although the manufacturer can do so.  This is&#xA;  fundamentally incompatible with the aim of protecting&#xA;  users&apos; freedom to change the software.  The systematic&#xA;  pattern of such abuse occurs in the area of products for&#xA;  individuals to use, which is precisely where it is most&#xA;  unacceptable.  Therefore, we have designed this version&#xA;  of the GPL to prohibit the practice for those products.&#xA;  If such problems arise substantially in other domains, we&#xA;  stand ready to extend this provision to those domains in&#xA;  future versions of the GPL, as needed to protect the&#xA;  freedom of users.&#xA;&#xA;  Finally, every program is threatened constantly by&#xA;  software patents. States should not allow patents to&#xA;  restrict development and use of software on general-&#xA;  purpose computers, but in those that do, we wish to avoid&#xA;  the special danger that patents applied to a free program&#xA;  could make it effectively proprietary.  To prevent this,&#xA;  the GPL assures that patents cannot be used to render the&#xA;  program non-free.&#xA;&#xA;  The precise terms and conditions for copying,&#xA;  distribution and modification follow.&#xA;&#xA;                       TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;  0. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;This License&quot; refers to version 3 of the GNU General&#xA;  Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Copyright&quot; also means copyright-like laws that apply to&#xA;  other kinds of works, such as semiconductor masks.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;The Program&quot; refers to any copyrightable work licensed&#xA;  under this License.  Each licensee is addressed as &quot;you&quot;.&#xA;  &quot;Licensees&quot; and &quot;recipients&quot; may be individuals or&#xA;  organizations.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;modify&quot; a work means to copy from or adapt all or&#xA;  part of the work in a fashion requiring copyright&#xA;  permission, other than the making of an exact copy.  The&#xA;  resulting work is called a &quot;modified version&quot; of the&#xA;  earlier work or a work &quot;based on&quot; the earlier work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;covered work&quot; means either the unmodified Program or a&#xA;  work based on the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;propagate&quot; a work means to do anything with it that,&#xA;  without permission, would make you directly or&#xA;  secondarily liable for infringement under applicable&#xA;  copyright law, except executing it on a computer or&#xA;  modifying a private copy.  Propagation includes copying,&#xA;  distribution (with or without modification), making&#xA;  available to the public, and in some countries other&#xA;  activities as well.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;convey&quot; a work means any kind of propagation that&#xA;  enables other parties to make or receive copies.  Mere&#xA;  interaction with a user through a computer network, with&#xA;  no transfer of a copy, is not conveying.&#xA;&#xA;  An interactive user interface displays &quot;Appropriate Legal&#xA;  Notices&quot; to the extent that it includes a convenient and&#xA;  prominently visible feature that (1) displays an&#xA;  appropriate copyright notice, and (2) tells the user that&#xA;  there is no warranty for the work (except to the extent&#xA;  that warranties are provided), that licensees may convey&#xA;  the work under this License, and how to view a copy of&#xA;  this License.  If the interface presents a list of user&#xA;  commands or options, such as a menu, a prominent item in&#xA;  the list meets this criterion.&#xA;&#xA;  1. Source Code.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;source code&quot; for a work means the preferred form of&#xA;  the work for making modifications to it.  &quot;Object code&quot;&#xA;  means any non-source form of a work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;Standard Interface&quot; means an interface that either is&#xA;  an official standard defined by a recognized standards&#xA;  body, or, in the case of interfaces specified for a&#xA;  particular programming language, one that is widely used&#xA;  among developers working in that language.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;System Libraries&quot; of an executable work include&#xA;  anything, other than the work as a whole, that (a) is&#xA;  included in the normal form of packaging a Major&#xA;  Component, but which is not part of that Major Component,&#xA;  and (b) serves only to enable use of the work with that&#xA;  Major Component, or to implement a Standard Interface for&#xA;  which an implementation is available to the public in&#xA;  source code form.  A &quot;Major Component&quot;, in this context,&#xA;  means a major essential component (kernel, window system,&#xA;  and so on) of the specific operating system (if any) on&#xA;  which the executable work runs, or a compiler used to&#xA;  produce the work, or an object code interpreter used to&#xA;  run it.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Corresponding Source&quot; for a work in object code form&#xA;  means all the source code needed to generate, install,&#xA;  and (for an executable work) run the object code and to&#xA;  modify the work, including scripts to control those&#xA;  activities.  However, it does not include the work&apos;s&#xA;  System Libraries, or general-purpose tools or generally&#xA;  available free programs which are used unmodified in&#xA;  performing those activities but which are not part of the&#xA;  work.  For example, Corresponding Source includes&#xA;  interface definition files associated with source files&#xA;  for the work, and the source code for shared libraries&#xA;  and dynamically linked subprograms that the work is&#xA;  specifically designed to require, such as by intimate&#xA;  data communication or control flow between those&#xA;  subprograms and other parts of the work.&#xA;&#xA;  The Corresponding Source need not include anything that&#xA;  users can regenerate automatically from other parts of&#xA;  the Corresponding Source.&#xA;&#xA;  The Corresponding Source for a work in source code form&#xA;  is that same work.&#xA;&#xA;  2. Basic Permissions.&#xA;&#xA;  All rights granted under this License are granted for the&#xA;  term of copyright on the Program, and are irrevocable&#xA;  provided the stated conditions are met.  This License&#xA;  explicitly affirms your unlimited permission to run the&#xA;  unmodified Program.  The output from running a covered&#xA;  work is covered by this License only if the output, given&#xA;  its content, constitutes a covered work.  This License&#xA;  acknowledges your rights of fair use or other equivalent,&#xA;  as provided by copyright law.&#xA;&#xA;  You may make, run and propagate covered works that you do&#xA;  not convey, without conditions so long as your license&#xA;  otherwise remains in force.  You may convey covered works&#xA;  to others for the sole purpose of having them make&#xA;  modifications exclusively for you, or provide you with&#xA;  facilities for running those works, provided that you&#xA;  comply with the terms of this License in conveying all&#xA;  material for which you do not control copyright.  Those&#xA;  thus making or running the covered works for you must do&#xA;  so exclusively on your behalf, under your direction and&#xA;  control, on terms that prohibit them from making any&#xA;  copies of your copyrighted material outside their&#xA;  relationship with you.&#xA;&#xA;  Conveying under any other circumstances is permitted&#xA;  solely under the conditions stated below.  Sublicensing&#xA;  is not allowed; section 10 makes it unnecessary.&#xA;&#xA;  3. Protecting Users&apos; Legal Rights From Anti-Circumvention&#xA;  Law.&#xA;&#xA;  No covered work shall be deemed part of an effective&#xA;  technological measure under any applicable law fulfilling&#xA;  obligations under article 11 of the WIPO copyright treaty&#xA;  adopted on 20 December 1996, or similar laws prohibiting&#xA;  or restricting circumvention of such measures.&#xA;&#xA;  When you convey a covered work, you waive any legal power&#xA;  to forbid circumvention of technological measures to the&#xA;  extent such circumvention is effected by exercising&#xA;  rights under this License with respect to the covered&#xA;  work, and you disclaim any intention to limit operation&#xA;  or modification of the work as a means of enforcing,&#xA;  against the work&apos;s users, your or third parties&apos; legal&#xA;  rights to forbid circumvention of technological measures.&#xA;&#xA;  4. Conveying Verbatim Copies.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey verbatim copies of the Program&apos;s source&#xA;  code as you receive it, in any medium, provided that you&#xA;  conspicuously and appropriately publish on each copy an&#xA;  appropriate copyright notice; keep intact all notices&#xA;  stating that this License and any non-permissive terms&#xA;  added in accord with section 7 apply to the code; keep&#xA;  intact all notices of the absence of any warranty; and&#xA;  give all recipients a copy of this License along with the&#xA;  Program.&#xA;&#xA;  You may charge any price or no price for each copy that&#xA;  you convey, and you may offer support or warranty&#xA;  protection for a fee.&#xA;&#xA;  5. Conveying Modified Source Versions.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a work based on the Program, or the&#xA;  modifications to produce it from the Program, in the form&#xA;  of source code under the terms of section 4, provided&#xA;  that you also meet all of these conditions:&#xA;&#xA;    a) The work must carry prominent notices stating that&#xA;    you modified it, and giving a relevant date.&#xA;&#xA;    b) The work must carry prominent notices stating that&#xA;    it is released under this License and any conditions&#xA;    added under section 7.  This requirement modifies the&#xA;    requirement in section 4 to &quot;keep intact all notices&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;    c) You must license the entire work, as a whole, under&#xA;    this License to anyone who comes into possession of a&#xA;    copy.  This License will therefore apply, along with&#xA;    any applicable section 7 additional terms, to the whole&#xA;    of the work, and all its parts, regardless of how they&#xA;    are packaged.  This License gives no permission to&#xA;    license the work in any other way, but it does not&#xA;    invalidate such permission if you have separately&#xA;    received it.&#xA;&#xA;    d) If the work has interactive user interfaces, each&#xA;    must display Appropriate Legal Notices; however, if the&#xA;    Program has interactive interfaces that do not display&#xA;    Appropriate Legal Notices, your work need not make them&#xA;    do so.&#xA;&#xA;  A compilation of a covered work with other separate and&#xA;  independent works, which are not by their nature&#xA;  extensions of the covered work, and which are not&#xA;  combined with it such as to form a larger program, in or&#xA;  on a volume of a storage or distribution medium, is&#xA;  called an &quot;aggregate&quot; if the compilation and its&#xA;  resulting copyright are not used to limit the access or&#xA;  legal rights of the compilation&apos;s users beyond what the&#xA;  individual works permit.  Inclusion of a covered work in&#xA;  an aggregate does not cause this License to apply to the&#xA;  other parts of the aggregate.&#xA;&#xA;  6. Conveying Non-Source Forms.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a covered work in object code form under&#xA;  the terms of sections 4 and 5, provided that you also&#xA;  convey the machine-readable Corresponding Source under&#xA;  the terms of this License, in one of these ways:&#xA;&#xA;    a) Convey the object code in, or embodied in, a&#xA;    physical product (including a physical distribution&#xA;    medium), accompanied by the Corresponding Source fixed&#xA;    on a durable physical medium customarily used for&#xA;    software interchange.&#xA;&#xA;    b) Convey the object code in, or embodied in, a&#xA;    physical product (including a physical distribution&#xA;    medium), accompanied by a written offer, valid for at&#xA;    least three years and valid for as long as you offer&#xA;    spare parts or customer support for that product model,&#xA;    to give anyone who possesses the object code either (1)&#xA;    a copy of the Corresponding Source for all the software&#xA;    in the product that is covered by this License, on a&#xA;    durable physical medium customarily used for software&#xA;    interchange, for a price no more than your reasonable&#xA;    cost of physically performing this conveying of source,&#xA;    or (2) access to copy the Corresponding Source from a&#xA;    network server at no charge.&#xA;&#xA;    c) Convey individual copies of the object code with a&#xA;    copy of the written offer to provide the Corresponding&#xA;    Source.  This alternative is allowed only occasionally&#xA;    and noncommercially, and only if you received the&#xA;    object code with such an offer, in accord with&#xA;    subsection 6b.&#xA;&#xA;    d) Convey the object code by offering access from a&#xA;    designated place (gratis or for a charge), and offer&#xA;    equivalent access to the Corresponding Source in the&#xA;    same way through the same place at no further charge.&#xA;    You need not require recipients to copy the&#xA;    Corresponding Source along with the object code.  If&#xA;    the place to copy the object code is a network server,&#xA;    the Corresponding Source may be on a different server (&#xA;    operated by you or a third party) that supports&#xA;    equivalent copying facilities, provided you maintain&#xA;    clear directions next to the object code saying where&#xA;    to find the Corresponding Source.  Regardless of what&#xA;    server hosts the Corresponding Source, you remain&#xA;    obligated to ensure that it is available for as long as&#xA;    needed to satisfy these requirements.&#xA;&#xA;    e) Convey the object code using peer-to-peer&#xA;    transmission, provided you inform other peers where the&#xA;    object code and Corresponding Source of the work are&#xA;    being offered to the general public at no charge under&#xA;    subsection 6d.&#xA;&#xA;  A separable portion of the object code, whose source code&#xA;  is excluded from the Corresponding Source as a System&#xA;  Library, need not be included in conveying the object&#xA;  code work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;User Product&quot; is either (1) a &quot;consumer product&quot;,&#xA;  which means any tangible personal property which is&#xA;  normally used for personal, family, or household purposes,&#xA;  or (2) anything designed or sold for incorporation into a&#xA;  dwelling.  In determining whether a product is a consumer&#xA;  product, doubtful cases shall be resolved in favor of&#xA;  coverage.  For a particular product received by a&#xA;  particular user, &quot;normally used&quot; refers to a typical or&#xA;  common use of that class of product, regardless of the&#xA;  status of the particular user or of the way in which the&#xA;  particular user actually uses, or expects or is expected&#xA;  to use, the product.  A product is a consumer product&#xA;  regardless of whether the product has substantial&#xA;  commercial, industrial or non-consumer uses, unless such&#xA;  uses represent the only significant mode of use of the&#xA;  product.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Installation Information&quot; for a User Product means any&#xA;  methods, procedures, authorization keys, or other&#xA;  information required to install and execute modified&#xA;  versions of a covered work in that User Product from a&#xA;  modified version of its Corresponding Source.  The&#xA;  information must suffice to ensure that the continued&#xA;  functioning of the modified object code is in no case&#xA;  prevented or interfered with solely because modification&#xA;  has been made.&#xA;&#xA;  If you convey an object code work under this section in,&#xA;  or with, or specifically for use in, a User Product, and&#xA;  the conveying occurs as part of a transaction in which&#xA;  the right of possession and use of the User Product is&#xA;  transferred to the recipient in perpetuity or for a fixed&#xA;  term (regardless of how the transaction is characterized),&#xA;  the Corresponding Source conveyed under this section must&#xA;  be accompanied by the Installation Information.  But this&#xA;  requirement does not apply if neither you nor any third&#xA;  party retains the ability to install modified object code&#xA;  on the User Product (for example, the work has been&#xA;  installed in ROM).&#xA;&#xA;  The requirement to provide Installation Information does&#xA;  not include a requirement to continue to provide support&#xA;  service, warranty, or updates for a work that has been&#xA;  modified or installed by the recipient, or for the User&#xA;  Product in which it has been modified or installed.&#xA;  Access to a network may be denied when the modification&#xA;  itself materially and adversely affects the operation of&#xA;  the network or violates the rules and protocols for&#xA;  communication across the network.&#xA;&#xA;  Corresponding Source conveyed, and Installation&#xA;  Information provided, in accord with this section must be&#xA;  in a format that is publicly documented (and with an&#xA;  implementation available to the public in source code&#xA;  form), and must require no special password or key for&#xA;  unpacking, reading or copying.&#xA;&#xA;  7. Additional Terms.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Additional permissions&quot; are terms that supplement the&#xA;  terms of this License by making exceptions from one or&#xA;  more of its conditions. Additional permissions that are&#xA;  applicable to the entire Program shall be treated as&#xA;  though they were included in this License, to the extent&#xA;  that they are valid under applicable law.  If additional&#xA;  permissions apply only to part of the Program, that part&#xA;  may be used separately under those permissions, but the&#xA;  entire Program remains governed by this License without&#xA;  regard to the additional permissions.&#xA;&#xA;  When you convey a copy of a covered work, you may at your&#xA;  option remove any additional permissions from that copy,&#xA;  or from any part of it.  (Additional permissions may be&#xA;  written to require their own removal in certain cases&#xA;  when you modify the work.)  You may place additional&#xA;  permissions on material, added by you to a covered work,&#xA;  for which you have or can give appropriate copyright&#xA;  permission.&#xA;&#xA;  Notwithstanding any other provision of this License, for&#xA;  material you add to a covered work, you may (if&#xA;  authorized by the copyright holders of that material)&#xA;  supplement the terms of this License with terms:&#xA;&#xA;    a) Disclaiming warranty or limiting liability&#xA;    differently from the terms of sections 15 and 16 of&#xA;    this License; or&#xA;&#xA;    b) Requiring preservation of specified reasonable legal&#xA;    notices or author attributions in that material or in&#xA;    the Appropriate Legal Notices displayed by works&#xA;    containing it; or&#xA;&#xA;    c) Prohibiting misrepresentation of the origin of that&#xA;    material, or requiring that modified versions of such&#xA;    material be marked in reasonable ways as different from&#xA;    the original version; or&#xA;&#xA;    d) Limiting the use for publicity purposes of names of&#xA;    licensors or authors of the material; or&#xA;&#xA;    e) Declining to grant rights under trademark law for&#xA;    use of some trade names, trademarks, or service marks;&#xA;    or&#xA;&#xA;    f) Requiring indemnification of licensors and authors&#xA;    of that material by anyone who conveys the material (or&#xA;    modified versions of it) with contractual assumptions&#xA;    of liability to the recipient, for any liability that&#xA;    these contractual assumptions directly impose on those&#xA;    licensors and authors.&#xA;&#xA;  All other non-permissive additional terms are considered &quot;&#xA;  further restrictions&quot; within the meaning of section 10.&#xA;  If the Program as you received it, or any part of it,&#xA;  contains a notice stating that it is governed by this&#xA;  License along with a term that is a further restriction,&#xA;  you may remove that term.  If a license document contains&#xA;  a further restriction but permits relicensing or&#xA;  conveying under this License, you may add to a covered&#xA;  work material governed by the terms of that license&#xA;  document, provided that the further restriction does not&#xA;  survive such relicensing or conveying.&#xA;&#xA;  If you add terms to a covered work in accord with this&#xA;  section, you must place, in the relevant source files, a&#xA;  statement of the additional terms that apply to those&#xA;  files, or a notice indicating where to find the&#xA;  applicable terms.&#xA;&#xA;  Additional terms, permissive or non-permissive, may be&#xA;  stated in the form of a separately written license, or&#xA;  stated as exceptions; the above requirements apply either&#xA;  way.&#xA;&#xA;  8. Termination.&#xA;&#xA;  You may not propagate or modify a covered work except as&#xA;  expressly provided under this License.  Any attempt&#xA;  otherwise to propagate or modify it is void, and will&#xA;  automatically terminate your rights under this License (&#xA;  including any patent licenses granted under the third&#xA;  paragraph of section 11).&#xA;&#xA;  However, if you cease all violation of this License, then&#xA;  your license from a particular copyright holder is&#xA;  reinstated (a) provisionally, unless and until the&#xA;  copyright holder explicitly and finally terminates your&#xA;  license, and (b) permanently, if the copyright holder&#xA;  fails to notify you of the violation by some reasonable&#xA;  means prior to 60 days after the cessation.&#xA;&#xA;  Moreover, your license from a particular copyright holder&#xA;  is reinstated permanently if the copyright holder&#xA;  notifies you of the violation by some reasonable means,&#xA;  this is the first time you have received notice of&#xA;  violation of this License (for any work) from that&#xA;  copyright holder, and you cure the violation prior to 30&#xA;  days after your receipt of the notice.&#xA;&#xA;  Termination of your rights under this section does not&#xA;  terminate the licenses of parties who have received&#xA;  copies or rights from you under this License.  If your&#xA;  rights have been terminated and not permanently&#xA;  reinstated, you do not qualify to receive new licenses&#xA;  for the same material under section 10.&#xA;&#xA;  9. Acceptance Not Required for Having Copies.&#xA;&#xA;  You are not required to accept this License in order to&#xA;  receive or run a copy of the Program.  Ancillary&#xA;  propagation of a covered work occurring solely as a&#xA;  consequence of using peer-to-peer transmission to receive&#xA;  a copy likewise does not require acceptance.  However,&#xA;  nothing other than this License grants you permission to&#xA;  propagate or modify any covered work.  These actions&#xA;  infringe copyright if you do not accept this License.&#xA;  Therefore, by modifying or propagating a covered work,&#xA;  you indicate your acceptance of this License to do so.&#xA;&#xA;  10. Automatic Licensing of Downstream Recipients.&#xA;&#xA;  Each time you convey a covered work, the recipient&#xA;  automatically receives a license from the original&#xA;  licensors, to run, modify and propagate that work,&#xA;  subject to this License.  You are not responsible for&#xA;  enforcing compliance by third parties with this License.&#xA;&#xA;  An &quot;entity transaction&quot; is a transaction transferring&#xA;  control of an organization, or substantially all assets&#xA;  of one, or subdividing an organization, or merging&#xA;  organizations.  If propagation of a covered work results&#xA;  from an entity transaction, each party to that&#xA;  transaction who receives a copy of the work also receives&#xA;  whatever licenses to the work the party&apos;s predecessor in&#xA;  interest had or could give under the previous paragraph,&#xA;  plus a right to possession of the Corresponding Source of&#xA;  the work from the predecessor in interest, if the&#xA;  predecessor has it or can get it with reasonable efforts.&#xA;&#xA;  You may not impose any further restrictions on the&#xA;  exercise of the rights granted or affirmed under this&#xA;  License.  For example, you may not impose a license fee,&#xA;  royalty, or other charge for exercise of rights granted&#xA;  under this License, and you may not initiate litigation (&#xA;  including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit)&#xA;  alleging that any patent claim is infringed by making,&#xA;  using, selling, offering for sale, or importing the&#xA;  Program or any portion of it.&#xA;&#xA;  11. Patents.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;contributor&quot; is a copyright holder who authorizes use&#xA;  under this License of the Program or a work on which the&#xA;  Program is based.  The work thus licensed is called the&#xA;  contributor&apos;s &quot;contributor version&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;  A contributor&apos;s &quot;essential patent claims&quot; are all patent&#xA;  claims owned or controlled by the contributor, whether&#xA;  already acquired or hereafter acquired, that would be&#xA;  infringed by some manner, permitted by this License, of&#xA;  making, using, or selling its contributor version, but do&#xA;  not include claims that would be infringed only as a&#xA;  consequence of further modification of the contributor&#xA;  version.  For purposes of this definition, &quot;control&quot;&#xA;  includes the right to grant patent sublicenses in a&#xA;  manner consistent with the requirements of this License.&#xA;&#xA;  Each contributor grants you a non-exclusive, worldwide,&#xA;  royalty-free patent license under the contributor&apos;s&#xA;  essential patent claims, to make, use, sell, offer for&#xA;  sale, import and otherwise run, modify and propagate the&#xA;  contents of its contributor version.&#xA;&#xA;  In the following three paragraphs, a &quot;patent license&quot; is&#xA;  any express agreement or commitment, however denominated,&#xA;  not to enforce a patent (such as an express permission to&#xA;  practice a patent or covenant not to sue for patent&#xA;  infringement).  To &quot;grant&quot; such a patent license to a&#xA;  party means to make such an agreement or commitment not&#xA;  to enforce a patent against the party.&#xA;&#xA;  If you convey a covered work, knowingly relying on a&#xA;  patent license, and the Corresponding Source of the work&#xA;  is not available for anyone to copy, free of charge and&#xA;  under the terms of this License, through a publicly&#xA;  available network server or other readily accessible&#xA;  means, then you must either (1) cause the Corresponding&#xA;  Source to be so available, or (2) arrange to deprive&#xA;  yourself of the benefit of the patent license for this&#xA;  particular work, or (3) arrange, in a manner consistent&#xA;  with the requirements of this License, to extend the&#xA;  patent license to downstream recipients.  &quot;Knowingly&#xA;  relying&quot; means you have actual knowledge that, but for&#xA;  the patent license, your conveying the covered work in a&#xA;  country, or your recipient&apos;s use of the covered work in a&#xA;  country, would infringe one or more identifiable patents&#xA;  in that country that you have reason to believe are valid.&#xA;&#xA;  If, pursuant to or in connection with a single&#xA;  transaction or arrangement, you convey, or propagate by&#xA;  procuring conveyance of, a covered work, and grant a&#xA;  patent license to some of the parties receiving the&#xA;  covered work authorizing them to use, propagate, modify&#xA;  or convey a specific copy of the covered work, then the&#xA;  patent license you grant is automatically extended to all&#xA;  recipients of the covered work and works based on it.&#xA;&#xA;  A patent license is &quot;discriminatory&quot; if it does not&#xA;  include within the scope of its coverage, prohibits the&#xA;  exercise of, or is conditioned on the non-exercise of one&#xA;  or more of the rights that are specifically granted under&#xA;  this License.  You may not convey a covered work if you&#xA;  are a party to an arrangement with a third party that is&#xA;  in the business of distributing software, under which you&#xA;  make payment to the third party based on the extent of&#xA;  your activity of conveying the work, and under which the&#xA;  third party grants, to any of the parties who would&#xA;  receive the covered work from you, a discriminatory&#xA;  patent license (a) in connection with copies of the&#xA;  covered work conveyed by you (or copies made from those&#xA;  copies), or (b) primarily for and in connection with&#xA;  specific products or compilations that contain the&#xA;  covered work, unless you entered into that arrangement,&#xA;  or that patent license was granted, prior to 28 March&#xA;  2007.&#xA;&#xA;  Nothing in this License shall be construed as excluding&#xA;  or limiting any implied license or other defenses to&#xA;  infringement that may otherwise be available to you under&#xA;  applicable patent law.&#xA;&#xA;  12. No Surrender of Others&apos; Freedom.&#xA;&#xA;  If conditions are imposed on you (whether by court order,&#xA;  agreement or otherwise) that contradict the conditions of&#xA;  this License, they do not excuse you from the conditions&#xA;  of this License.  If you cannot convey a covered work so&#xA;  as to satisfy simultaneously your obligations under this&#xA;  License and any other pertinent obligations, then as a&#xA;  consequence you may not convey it at all.  For example,&#xA;  if you agree to terms that obligate you to collect a&#xA;  royalty for further conveying from those to whom you&#xA;  convey the Program, the only way you could satisfy both&#xA;  those terms and this License would be to refrain entirely&#xA;  from conveying the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  13. Use with the GNU Affero General Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  Notwithstanding any other provision of this License, you&#xA;  have permission to link or combine any covered work with&#xA;  a work licensed under version 3 of the GNU Affero General&#xA;  Public License into a single combined work, and to convey&#xA;  the resulting work.  The terms of this License will&#xA;  continue to apply to the part which is the covered work,&#xA;  but the special requirements of the GNU Affero General&#xA;  Public License, section 13, concerning interaction&#xA;  through a network will apply to the combination as such.&#xA;&#xA;  14. Revised Versions of this License.&#xA;&#xA;  The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or&#xA;  new versions of the GNU General Public License from time&#xA;  to time.  Such new versions will be similar in spirit to&#xA;  the present version, but may differ in detail to address&#xA;  new problems or concerns.&#xA;&#xA;  Each version is given a distinguishing version number.&#xA;  If the Program specifies that a certain numbered version&#xA;  of the GNU General Public License &quot;or any later version&quot;&#xA;  applies to it, you have the option of following the terms&#xA;  and conditions either of that numbered version or of any&#xA;  later version published by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;  If the Program does not specify a version number of the&#xA;  GNU General Public License, you may choose any version&#xA;  ever published by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;&#xA;  If the Program specifies that a proxy can decide which&#xA;  future versions of the GNU General Public License can be&#xA;  used, that proxy&apos;s public statement of acceptance of a&#xA;  version permanently authorizes you to choose that version&#xA;  for the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  Later license versions may give you additional or&#xA;  different permissions.  However, no additional&#xA;  obligations are imposed on any author or copyright holder&#xA;  as a result of your choosing to follow a later version.&#xA;&#xA;  15. Disclaimer of Warranty.&#xA;&#xA;  THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE PROGRAM, TO THE EXTENT&#xA;  PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.  EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE&#xA;  STATED IN WRITING THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER&#xA;  PARTIES PROVIDE THE PROGRAM &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF&#xA;  ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT&#xA;  LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND&#xA;  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO&#xA;  THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE PROGRAM IS WITH YOU.&#xA;  SHOULD THE PROGRAM PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE COST&#xA;  OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.&#xA;&#xA;  16. Limitation of Liability.&#xA;&#xA;  IN NO EVENT UNLESS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW OR AGREED&#xA;  TO IN WRITING WILL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER&#xA;  PARTY WHO MODIFIES AND/OR CONVEYS THE PROGRAM AS&#xA;  PERMITTED ABOVE, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES, INCLUDING&#xA;  ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES&#xA;  ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE PROGRAM (&#xA;  INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING&#xA;  RENDERED INACCURATE OR LOSSES SUSTAINED BY YOU OR THIRD&#xA;  PARTIES OR A FAILURE OF THE PROGRAM TO OPERATE WITH ANY&#xA;  OTHER PROGRAMS), EVEN IF SUCH HOLDER OR OTHER PARTY HAS&#xA;  BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;  17. Interpretation of Sections 15 and 16.&#xA;&#xA;  If the disclaimer of warranty and limitation of liability&#xA;  provided above cannot be given local legal effect&#xA;  according to their terms, reviewing courts shall apply&#xA;  local law that most closely approximates an absolute&#xA;  waiver of all civil liability in connection with the&#xA;  Program, unless a warranty or assumption of liability&#xA;  accompanies a copy of the Program in return for a fee.&#xA;  &#xA;       GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE&#xA;                       Version 3, 29 June 2007&#xA;&#xA; Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. &lt;http://&#xA; fsf.org/&gt; Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute&#xA; verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it&#xA; is not allowed.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;  This version of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  incorporates the terms and conditions of version 3 of the&#xA;  GNU General Public License, supplemented by the&#xA;  additional permissions listed below.&#xA;&#xA;  0. Additional Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;  As used herein, &quot;this License&quot; refers to version 3 of the&#xA;  GNU Lesser General Public License, and the &quot;GNU GPL&quot;&#xA;  refers to version 3 of the GNU General Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;The Library&quot; refers to a covered work governed by this&#xA;  License, other than an Application or a Combined Work as&#xA;  defined below.&#xA;&#xA;  An &quot;Application&quot; is any work that makes use of an&#xA;  interface provided by the Library, but which is not&#xA;  otherwise based on the Library. Defining a subclass of a&#xA;  class defined by the Library is deemed a mode of using an&#xA;  interface provided by the Library.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;Combined Work&quot; is a work produced by combining or&#xA;  linking an Application with the Library.  The particular&#xA;  version of the Library with which the Combined Work was&#xA;  made is also called the &quot;Linked Version&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Minimal Corresponding Source&quot; for a Combined Work&#xA;  means the Corresponding Source for the Combined Work,&#xA;  excluding any source code for portions of the Combined&#xA;  Work that, considered in isolation, are based on the&#xA;  Application, and not on the Linked Version.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Corresponding Application Code&quot; for a Combined Work&#xA;  means the object code and/or source code for the&#xA;  Application, including any data and utility programs&#xA;  needed for reproducing the Combined Work from the&#xA;  Application, but excluding the System Libraries of the&#xA;  Combined Work.&#xA;&#xA;  1. Exception to Section 3 of the GNU GPL.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a covered work under sections 3 and 4 of&#xA;  this License without being bound by section 3 of the GNU&#xA;  GPL.&#xA;&#xA;  2. Conveying Modified Versions.&#xA;&#xA;  If you modify a copy of the Library, and, in your&#xA;  modifications, a facility refers to a function or data to&#xA;  be supplied by an Application that uses the facility (&#xA;  other than as an argument passed when the facility is&#xA;  invoked), then you may convey a copy of the modified&#xA;  version:&#xA;&#xA;   a) under this License, provided that you make a good&#xA;   faith effort to ensure that, in the event an Application&#xA;   does not supply the function or data, the facility still&#xA;   operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose&#xA;   remains meaningful, or&#xA;&#xA;   b) under the GNU GPL, with none of the additional&#xA;   permissions of this License applicable to that copy.&#xA;&#xA;  3. Object Code Incorporating Material from Library Header&#xA;  Files.&#xA;&#xA;  The object code form of an Application may incorporate&#xA;  material from a header file that is part of the Library.&#xA;  You may convey such object code under terms of your&#xA;  choice, provided that, if the incorporated material is&#xA;  not limited to numerical parameters, data structure&#xA;  layouts and accessors, or small macros, inline functions&#xA;  and templates (ten or fewer lines in length), you do both&#xA;  of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the object&#xA;   code that the Library is used in it and that the Library&#xA;   and its use are covered by this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Accompany the object code with a copy of the GNU GPL&#xA;   and this license document.&#xA;&#xA;  4. Combined Works.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a Combined Work under terms of your choice&#xA;  that, taken together, effectively do not restrict&#xA;  modification of the portions of the Library contained in&#xA;  the Combined Work and reverse engineering for debugging&#xA;  such modifications, if you also do each of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the Combined&#xA;   Work that the Library is used in it and that the Library&#xA;   and its use are covered by this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Accompany the Combined Work with a copy of the GNU&#xA;   GPL and this license document.&#xA;&#xA;   c) For a Combined Work that displays copyright notices&#xA;   during execution, include the copyright notice for the&#xA;   Library among these notices, as well as a reference&#xA;   directing the user to the copies of the GNU GPL and this&#xA;   license document.&#xA;&#xA;   d) Do one of the following:&#xA;&#xA;       0) Convey the Minimal Corresponding Source under the&#xA;       terms of this License, and the Corresponding&#xA;       Application Code in a form suitable for, and under&#xA;       terms that permit, the user to recombine or relink&#xA;       the Application with a modified version of the&#xA;       Linked Version to produce a modified Combined Work,&#xA;       in the manner specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL&#xA;       for conveying Corresponding Source.&#xA;&#xA;       1) Use a suitable shared library mechanism for&#xA;       linking with the Library.  A suitable mechanism is&#xA;       one that (a) uses at run time a copy of the Library&#xA;       already present on the user&apos;s computer system, and (&#xA;       b) will operate properly with a modified version of&#xA;       the Library that is interface-compatible with the&#xA;       Linked Version.&#xA;&#xA;   e) Provide Installation Information, but only if you&#xA;   would otherwise be required to provide such information&#xA;   under section 6 of the GNU GPL, and only to the extent&#xA;   that such information is necessary to install and&#xA;   execute a modified version of the Combined Work produced&#xA;   by recombining or relinking the Application with a&#xA;   modified version of the Linked Version. (If you use&#xA;   option 4d0, the Installation Information must accompany&#xA;   the Minimal Corresponding Source and Corresponding&#xA;   Application Code. If you use option 4d1, you must&#xA;   provide the Installation Information in the manner&#xA;   specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL for conveying&#xA;   Corresponding Source.)&#xA;&#xA;  5. Combined Libraries.&#xA;&#xA;  You may place library facilities that are a work based on&#xA;  the Library side by side in a single library together&#xA;  with other library facilities that are not Applications&#xA;  and are not covered by this License, and convey such a&#xA;  combined library under terms of your choice, if you do&#xA;  both of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the&#xA;   same work based on the Library, uncombined with any&#xA;   other library facilities, conveyed under the terms of&#xA;   this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Give prominent notice with the combined library that&#xA;   part of it is a work based on the Library, and&#xA;   explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined&#xA;   form of the same work.&#xA;&#xA;  6. Revised Versions of the GNU Lesser General Public&#xA;  License.&#xA;&#xA;  The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or&#xA;  new versions of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in&#xA;  spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail&#xA;  to address new problems or concerns.&#xA;&#xA;  Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If&#xA;  the Library as you received it specifies that a certain&#xA;  numbered version of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  &quot;or any later version&quot; applies to it, you have the option&#xA;  of following the terms and conditions either of that&#xA;  published version or of any later version published by&#xA;  the Free Software Foundation. If the Library as you&#xA;  received it does not specify a version number of the GNU&#xA;  Lesser General Public License, you may choose any version&#xA;  of the GNU Lesser General Public License ever published&#xA;  by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;&#xA;  If the Library as you received it specifies that a proxy&#xA;  can decide whether future versions of the GNU Lesser&#xA;  General Public License shall apply, that proxy&apos;s public&#xA;  statement of acceptance of any version is permanent&#xA;  authorization for you to choose that version for the&#xA;  Library.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2004-2008 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.jar' version='1.3.0'>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='FreeMemFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='FreeMem is a graphical memory monitor. Features include:&#xA;Short and long term memory monitor, manual and automatic garbage collection, Preferences, etc.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='junginger.biz'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.jar' version='1.3.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature' version='1.3.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature' version='1.3.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;You are free:&#xA;* to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;* to make commercial use of the work&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon&#xA;this work.&#xA;* For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others&#xA;the license terms of this work.&#xA;* Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission&#xA;from the copyright holder.&#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2005 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.2.5' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' range='[0.0.0,1.2.5)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.2.5'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.2.5'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' version='1.2.5'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.2.5&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' version='1.2.5' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.2.5)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='RssViewFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='RSS View is an RSS/Atom reader that keeps you always up-to-date. Unlike standard news readers, it is designed to integrate into Eclipse. Thus, you have everything at one place. RSS View may even improve your development process by integrating your bug tracker, development forum or wiki directly in your IDE.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' version='1.2.5'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='5'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.rss.eclipse.RssPlugin' range='[1.2.5,1.2.5]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' range='[1.2.5,1.2.5]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;&#xA;You are free:&#xA;&#xA;    * to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;    * to make commercial use of the work&#xA;&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon this work.&#xA;&#xA;    * For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others the license terms of this work.&#xA;    * Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission from the copyright holder.&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2007 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.group' version='1.0.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='ExploreFS Feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='Open the folder of any selected item directly in Windows Explorer'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='www.junginger.biz'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.group' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='6'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.2.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.jdt.core' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' range='[1.0.0,1.0.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.jar' range='[1.0.0,1.0.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;You are free:&#xA;* to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;* to make commercial use of the work&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon&#xA;this work.&#xA;* For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others&#xA;the license terms of this work.&#xA;* Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission&#xA;from the copyright holder.&#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2007 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0.2--cMVXvE'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='ExploreFS'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0.2--cMVXvE'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.group' range='[1.0.0,1.0.0]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS' version='1.0.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: biz.junginger.ExploreFS&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.0.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.group' version='1.3.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.3.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='FreeMemFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='FreeMem is a graphical memory monitor. Features include:&#xA;Short and long term memory monitor, manual and automatic garbage collection, Preferences, etc.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='junginger.biz'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.group' version='1.3.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='3'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.freemem.FreeMem' range='[1.3.0,1.3.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.jar' range='[1.3.0,1.3.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;You are free:&#xA;* to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;* to make commercial use of the work&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon&#xA;this work.&#xA;* For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others&#xA;the license terms of this work.&#xA;* Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission&#xA;from the copyright holder.&#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2005 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' version='1.5.0'>
      <properties size='3'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='RssViewFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='RSS View newsfeed reader with a compact UI for Eclipse 3.2+.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' version='1.5.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature' version='1.5.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature' version='1.5.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html' url='http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html'>
          GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE&#xA;                       Version 3, 29 June 2007&#xA;&#xA; Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. &lt;http://&#xA; fsf.org/&gt; Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute&#xA; verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it&#xA; is not allowed.&#xA;&#xA;                            Preamble&#xA;&#xA;  The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft&#xA;  license for software and other kinds of works.&#xA;&#xA;  The licenses for most software and other practical works&#xA;  are designed to take away your freedom to share and&#xA;  change the works.  By contrast, the GNU General Public&#xA;  License is intended to guarantee your freedom to share&#xA;  and change all versions of a program--to make sure it&#xA;  remains free software for all its users.  We, the Free&#xA;  Software Foundation, use the GNU General Public License&#xA;  for most of our software; it applies also to any other&#xA;  work released this way by its authors.  You can apply it&#xA;  to your programs, too.&#xA;&#xA;  When we speak of free software, we are referring to&#xA;  freedom, not price.  Our General Public Licenses are&#xA;  designed to make sure that you have the freedom to&#xA;  distribute copies of free software (and charge for them&#xA;  if you wish), that you receive source code or can get it&#xA;  if you want it, that you can change the software or use&#xA;  pieces of it in new free programs, and that you know you&#xA;  can do these things.&#xA;&#xA;  To protect your rights, we need to prevent others from&#xA;  denying you these rights or asking you to surrender the&#xA;  rights.  Therefore, you have certain responsibilities if&#xA;  you distribute copies of the software, or if you modify&#xA;  it: responsibilities to respect the freedom of others.&#xA;&#xA;  For example, if you distribute copies of such a program,&#xA;  whether gratis or for a fee, you must pass on to the&#xA;  recipients the same freedoms that you received.  You must&#xA;  make sure that they, too, receive or can get the source&#xA;  code.  And you must show them these terms so they know&#xA;  their rights.&#xA;&#xA;  Developers that use the GNU GPL protect your rights with&#xA;  two steps: (1) assert copyright on the software, and (2)&#xA;  offer you this License giving you legal permission to&#xA;  copy, distribute and/or modify it.&#xA;&#xA;  For the developers&apos; and authors&apos; protection, the GPL&#xA;  clearly explains that there is no warranty for this free&#xA;  software.  For both users&apos; and authors&apos; sake, the GPL&#xA;  requires that modified versions be marked as changed, so&#xA;  that their problems will not be attributed erroneously to&#xA;  authors of previous versions.&#xA;&#xA;  Some devices are designed to deny users access to install&#xA;  or run modified versions of the software inside them,&#xA;  although the manufacturer can do so.  This is&#xA;  fundamentally incompatible with the aim of protecting&#xA;  users&apos; freedom to change the software.  The systematic&#xA;  pattern of such abuse occurs in the area of products for&#xA;  individuals to use, which is precisely where it is most&#xA;  unacceptable.  Therefore, we have designed this version&#xA;  of the GPL to prohibit the practice for those products.&#xA;  If such problems arise substantially in other domains, we&#xA;  stand ready to extend this provision to those domains in&#xA;  future versions of the GPL, as needed to protect the&#xA;  freedom of users.&#xA;&#xA;  Finally, every program is threatened constantly by&#xA;  software patents. States should not allow patents to&#xA;  restrict development and use of software on general-&#xA;  purpose computers, but in those that do, we wish to avoid&#xA;  the special danger that patents applied to a free program&#xA;  could make it effectively proprietary.  To prevent this,&#xA;  the GPL assures that patents cannot be used to render the&#xA;  program non-free.&#xA;&#xA;  The precise terms and conditions for copying,&#xA;  distribution and modification follow.&#xA;&#xA;                       TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;  0. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;This License&quot; refers to version 3 of the GNU General&#xA;  Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Copyright&quot; also means copyright-like laws that apply to&#xA;  other kinds of works, such as semiconductor masks.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;The Program&quot; refers to any copyrightable work licensed&#xA;  under this License.  Each licensee is addressed as &quot;you&quot;.&#xA;  &quot;Licensees&quot; and &quot;recipients&quot; may be individuals or&#xA;  organizations.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;modify&quot; a work means to copy from or adapt all or&#xA;  part of the work in a fashion requiring copyright&#xA;  permission, other than the making of an exact copy.  The&#xA;  resulting work is called a &quot;modified version&quot; of the&#xA;  earlier work or a work &quot;based on&quot; the earlier work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;covered work&quot; means either the unmodified Program or a&#xA;  work based on the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;propagate&quot; a work means to do anything with it that,&#xA;  without permission, would make you directly or&#xA;  secondarily liable for infringement under applicable&#xA;  copyright law, except executing it on a computer or&#xA;  modifying a private copy.  Propagation includes copying,&#xA;  distribution (with or without modification), making&#xA;  available to the public, and in some countries other&#xA;  activities as well.&#xA;&#xA;  To &quot;convey&quot; a work means any kind of propagation that&#xA;  enables other parties to make or receive copies.  Mere&#xA;  interaction with a user through a computer network, with&#xA;  no transfer of a copy, is not conveying.&#xA;&#xA;  An interactive user interface displays &quot;Appropriate Legal&#xA;  Notices&quot; to the extent that it includes a convenient and&#xA;  prominently visible feature that (1) displays an&#xA;  appropriate copyright notice, and (2) tells the user that&#xA;  there is no warranty for the work (except to the extent&#xA;  that warranties are provided), that licensees may convey&#xA;  the work under this License, and how to view a copy of&#xA;  this License.  If the interface presents a list of user&#xA;  commands or options, such as a menu, a prominent item in&#xA;  the list meets this criterion.&#xA;&#xA;  1. Source Code.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;source code&quot; for a work means the preferred form of&#xA;  the work for making modifications to it.  &quot;Object code&quot;&#xA;  means any non-source form of a work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;Standard Interface&quot; means an interface that either is&#xA;  an official standard defined by a recognized standards&#xA;  body, or, in the case of interfaces specified for a&#xA;  particular programming language, one that is widely used&#xA;  among developers working in that language.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;System Libraries&quot; of an executable work include&#xA;  anything, other than the work as a whole, that (a) is&#xA;  included in the normal form of packaging a Major&#xA;  Component, but which is not part of that Major Component,&#xA;  and (b) serves only to enable use of the work with that&#xA;  Major Component, or to implement a Standard Interface for&#xA;  which an implementation is available to the public in&#xA;  source code form.  A &quot;Major Component&quot;, in this context,&#xA;  means a major essential component (kernel, window system,&#xA;  and so on) of the specific operating system (if any) on&#xA;  which the executable work runs, or a compiler used to&#xA;  produce the work, or an object code interpreter used to&#xA;  run it.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Corresponding Source&quot; for a work in object code form&#xA;  means all the source code needed to generate, install,&#xA;  and (for an executable work) run the object code and to&#xA;  modify the work, including scripts to control those&#xA;  activities.  However, it does not include the work&apos;s&#xA;  System Libraries, or general-purpose tools or generally&#xA;  available free programs which are used unmodified in&#xA;  performing those activities but which are not part of the&#xA;  work.  For example, Corresponding Source includes&#xA;  interface definition files associated with source files&#xA;  for the work, and the source code for shared libraries&#xA;  and dynamically linked subprograms that the work is&#xA;  specifically designed to require, such as by intimate&#xA;  data communication or control flow between those&#xA;  subprograms and other parts of the work.&#xA;&#xA;  The Corresponding Source need not include anything that&#xA;  users can regenerate automatically from other parts of&#xA;  the Corresponding Source.&#xA;&#xA;  The Corresponding Source for a work in source code form&#xA;  is that same work.&#xA;&#xA;  2. Basic Permissions.&#xA;&#xA;  All rights granted under this License are granted for the&#xA;  term of copyright on the Program, and are irrevocable&#xA;  provided the stated conditions are met.  This License&#xA;  explicitly affirms your unlimited permission to run the&#xA;  unmodified Program.  The output from running a covered&#xA;  work is covered by this License only if the output, given&#xA;  its content, constitutes a covered work.  This License&#xA;  acknowledges your rights of fair use or other equivalent,&#xA;  as provided by copyright law.&#xA;&#xA;  You may make, run and propagate covered works that you do&#xA;  not convey, without conditions so long as your license&#xA;  otherwise remains in force.  You may convey covered works&#xA;  to others for the sole purpose of having them make&#xA;  modifications exclusively for you, or provide you with&#xA;  facilities for running those works, provided that you&#xA;  comply with the terms of this License in conveying all&#xA;  material for which you do not control copyright.  Those&#xA;  thus making or running the covered works for you must do&#xA;  so exclusively on your behalf, under your direction and&#xA;  control, on terms that prohibit them from making any&#xA;  copies of your copyrighted material outside their&#xA;  relationship with you.&#xA;&#xA;  Conveying under any other circumstances is permitted&#xA;  solely under the conditions stated below.  Sublicensing&#xA;  is not allowed; section 10 makes it unnecessary.&#xA;&#xA;  3. Protecting Users&apos; Legal Rights From Anti-Circumvention&#xA;  Law.&#xA;&#xA;  No covered work shall be deemed part of an effective&#xA;  technological measure under any applicable law fulfilling&#xA;  obligations under article 11 of the WIPO copyright treaty&#xA;  adopted on 20 December 1996, or similar laws prohibiting&#xA;  or restricting circumvention of such measures.&#xA;&#xA;  When you convey a covered work, you waive any legal power&#xA;  to forbid circumvention of technological measures to the&#xA;  extent such circumvention is effected by exercising&#xA;  rights under this License with respect to the covered&#xA;  work, and you disclaim any intention to limit operation&#xA;  or modification of the work as a means of enforcing,&#xA;  against the work&apos;s users, your or third parties&apos; legal&#xA;  rights to forbid circumvention of technological measures.&#xA;&#xA;  4. Conveying Verbatim Copies.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey verbatim copies of the Program&apos;s source&#xA;  code as you receive it, in any medium, provided that you&#xA;  conspicuously and appropriately publish on each copy an&#xA;  appropriate copyright notice; keep intact all notices&#xA;  stating that this License and any non-permissive terms&#xA;  added in accord with section 7 apply to the code; keep&#xA;  intact all notices of the absence of any warranty; and&#xA;  give all recipients a copy of this License along with the&#xA;  Program.&#xA;&#xA;  You may charge any price or no price for each copy that&#xA;  you convey, and you may offer support or warranty&#xA;  protection for a fee.&#xA;&#xA;  5. Conveying Modified Source Versions.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a work based on the Program, or the&#xA;  modifications to produce it from the Program, in the form&#xA;  of source code under the terms of section 4, provided&#xA;  that you also meet all of these conditions:&#xA;&#xA;    a) The work must carry prominent notices stating that&#xA;    you modified it, and giving a relevant date.&#xA;&#xA;    b) The work must carry prominent notices stating that&#xA;    it is released under this License and any conditions&#xA;    added under section 7.  This requirement modifies the&#xA;    requirement in section 4 to &quot;keep intact all notices&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;    c) You must license the entire work, as a whole, under&#xA;    this License to anyone who comes into possession of a&#xA;    copy.  This License will therefore apply, along with&#xA;    any applicable section 7 additional terms, to the whole&#xA;    of the work, and all its parts, regardless of how they&#xA;    are packaged.  This License gives no permission to&#xA;    license the work in any other way, but it does not&#xA;    invalidate such permission if you have separately&#xA;    received it.&#xA;&#xA;    d) If the work has interactive user interfaces, each&#xA;    must display Appropriate Legal Notices; however, if the&#xA;    Program has interactive interfaces that do not display&#xA;    Appropriate Legal Notices, your work need not make them&#xA;    do so.&#xA;&#xA;  A compilation of a covered work with other separate and&#xA;  independent works, which are not by their nature&#xA;  extensions of the covered work, and which are not&#xA;  combined with it such as to form a larger program, in or&#xA;  on a volume of a storage or distribution medium, is&#xA;  called an &quot;aggregate&quot; if the compilation and its&#xA;  resulting copyright are not used to limit the access or&#xA;  legal rights of the compilation&apos;s users beyond what the&#xA;  individual works permit.  Inclusion of a covered work in&#xA;  an aggregate does not cause this License to apply to the&#xA;  other parts of the aggregate.&#xA;&#xA;  6. Conveying Non-Source Forms.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a covered work in object code form under&#xA;  the terms of sections 4 and 5, provided that you also&#xA;  convey the machine-readable Corresponding Source under&#xA;  the terms of this License, in one of these ways:&#xA;&#xA;    a) Convey the object code in, or embodied in, a&#xA;    physical product (including a physical distribution&#xA;    medium), accompanied by the Corresponding Source fixed&#xA;    on a durable physical medium customarily used for&#xA;    software interchange.&#xA;&#xA;    b) Convey the object code in, or embodied in, a&#xA;    physical product (including a physical distribution&#xA;    medium), accompanied by a written offer, valid for at&#xA;    least three years and valid for as long as you offer&#xA;    spare parts or customer support for that product model,&#xA;    to give anyone who possesses the object code either (1)&#xA;    a copy of the Corresponding Source for all the software&#xA;    in the product that is covered by this License, on a&#xA;    durable physical medium customarily used for software&#xA;    interchange, for a price no more than your reasonable&#xA;    cost of physically performing this conveying of source,&#xA;    or (2) access to copy the Corresponding Source from a&#xA;    network server at no charge.&#xA;&#xA;    c) Convey individual copies of the object code with a&#xA;    copy of the written offer to provide the Corresponding&#xA;    Source.  This alternative is allowed only occasionally&#xA;    and noncommercially, and only if you received the&#xA;    object code with such an offer, in accord with&#xA;    subsection 6b.&#xA;&#xA;    d) Convey the object code by offering access from a&#xA;    designated place (gratis or for a charge), and offer&#xA;    equivalent access to the Corresponding Source in the&#xA;    same way through the same place at no further charge.&#xA;    You need not require recipients to copy the&#xA;    Corresponding Source along with the object code.  If&#xA;    the place to copy the object code is a network server,&#xA;    the Corresponding Source may be on a different server (&#xA;    operated by you or a third party) that supports&#xA;    equivalent copying facilities, provided you maintain&#xA;    clear directions next to the object code saying where&#xA;    to find the Corresponding Source.  Regardless of what&#xA;    server hosts the Corresponding Source, you remain&#xA;    obligated to ensure that it is available for as long as&#xA;    needed to satisfy these requirements.&#xA;&#xA;    e) Convey the object code using peer-to-peer&#xA;    transmission, provided you inform other peers where the&#xA;    object code and Corresponding Source of the work are&#xA;    being offered to the general public at no charge under&#xA;    subsection 6d.&#xA;&#xA;  A separable portion of the object code, whose source code&#xA;  is excluded from the Corresponding Source as a System&#xA;  Library, need not be included in conveying the object&#xA;  code work.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;User Product&quot; is either (1) a &quot;consumer product&quot;,&#xA;  which means any tangible personal property which is&#xA;  normally used for personal, family, or household purposes,&#xA;  or (2) anything designed or sold for incorporation into a&#xA;  dwelling.  In determining whether a product is a consumer&#xA;  product, doubtful cases shall be resolved in favor of&#xA;  coverage.  For a particular product received by a&#xA;  particular user, &quot;normally used&quot; refers to a typical or&#xA;  common use of that class of product, regardless of the&#xA;  status of the particular user or of the way in which the&#xA;  particular user actually uses, or expects or is expected&#xA;  to use, the product.  A product is a consumer product&#xA;  regardless of whether the product has substantial&#xA;  commercial, industrial or non-consumer uses, unless such&#xA;  uses represent the only significant mode of use of the&#xA;  product.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Installation Information&quot; for a User Product means any&#xA;  methods, procedures, authorization keys, or other&#xA;  information required to install and execute modified&#xA;  versions of a covered work in that User Product from a&#xA;  modified version of its Corresponding Source.  The&#xA;  information must suffice to ensure that the continued&#xA;  functioning of the modified object code is in no case&#xA;  prevented or interfered with solely because modification&#xA;  has been made.&#xA;&#xA;  If you convey an object code work under this section in,&#xA;  or with, or specifically for use in, a User Product, and&#xA;  the conveying occurs as part of a transaction in which&#xA;  the right of possession and use of the User Product is&#xA;  transferred to the recipient in perpetuity or for a fixed&#xA;  term (regardless of how the transaction is characterized),&#xA;  the Corresponding Source conveyed under this section must&#xA;  be accompanied by the Installation Information.  But this&#xA;  requirement does not apply if neither you nor any third&#xA;  party retains the ability to install modified object code&#xA;  on the User Product (for example, the work has been&#xA;  installed in ROM).&#xA;&#xA;  The requirement to provide Installation Information does&#xA;  not include a requirement to continue to provide support&#xA;  service, warranty, or updates for a work that has been&#xA;  modified or installed by the recipient, or for the User&#xA;  Product in which it has been modified or installed.&#xA;  Access to a network may be denied when the modification&#xA;  itself materially and adversely affects the operation of&#xA;  the network or violates the rules and protocols for&#xA;  communication across the network.&#xA;&#xA;  Corresponding Source conveyed, and Installation&#xA;  Information provided, in accord with this section must be&#xA;  in a format that is publicly documented (and with an&#xA;  implementation available to the public in source code&#xA;  form), and must require no special password or key for&#xA;  unpacking, reading or copying.&#xA;&#xA;  7. Additional Terms.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;Additional permissions&quot; are terms that supplement the&#xA;  terms of this License by making exceptions from one or&#xA;  more of its conditions. Additional permissions that are&#xA;  applicable to the entire Program shall be treated as&#xA;  though they were included in this License, to the extent&#xA;  that they are valid under applicable law.  If additional&#xA;  permissions apply only to part of the Program, that part&#xA;  may be used separately under those permissions, but the&#xA;  entire Program remains governed by this License without&#xA;  regard to the additional permissions.&#xA;&#xA;  When you convey a copy of a covered work, you may at your&#xA;  option remove any additional permissions from that copy,&#xA;  or from any part of it.  (Additional permissions may be&#xA;  written to require their own removal in certain cases&#xA;  when you modify the work.)  You may place additional&#xA;  permissions on material, added by you to a covered work,&#xA;  for which you have or can give appropriate copyright&#xA;  permission.&#xA;&#xA;  Notwithstanding any other provision of this License, for&#xA;  material you add to a covered work, you may (if&#xA;  authorized by the copyright holders of that material)&#xA;  supplement the terms of this License with terms:&#xA;&#xA;    a) Disclaiming warranty or limiting liability&#xA;    differently from the terms of sections 15 and 16 of&#xA;    this License; or&#xA;&#xA;    b) Requiring preservation of specified reasonable legal&#xA;    notices or author attributions in that material or in&#xA;    the Appropriate Legal Notices displayed by works&#xA;    containing it; or&#xA;&#xA;    c) Prohibiting misrepresentation of the origin of that&#xA;    material, or requiring that modified versions of such&#xA;    material be marked in reasonable ways as different from&#xA;    the original version; or&#xA;&#xA;    d) Limiting the use for publicity purposes of names of&#xA;    licensors or authors of the material; or&#xA;&#xA;    e) Declining to grant rights under trademark law for&#xA;    use of some trade names, trademarks, or service marks;&#xA;    or&#xA;&#xA;    f) Requiring indemnification of licensors and authors&#xA;    of that material by anyone who conveys the material (or&#xA;    modified versions of it) with contractual assumptions&#xA;    of liability to the recipient, for any liability that&#xA;    these contractual assumptions directly impose on those&#xA;    licensors and authors.&#xA;&#xA;  All other non-permissive additional terms are considered &quot;&#xA;  further restrictions&quot; within the meaning of section 10.&#xA;  If the Program as you received it, or any part of it,&#xA;  contains a notice stating that it is governed by this&#xA;  License along with a term that is a further restriction,&#xA;  you may remove that term.  If a license document contains&#xA;  a further restriction but permits relicensing or&#xA;  conveying under this License, you may add to a covered&#xA;  work material governed by the terms of that license&#xA;  document, provided that the further restriction does not&#xA;  survive such relicensing or conveying.&#xA;&#xA;  If you add terms to a covered work in accord with this&#xA;  section, you must place, in the relevant source files, a&#xA;  statement of the additional terms that apply to those&#xA;  files, or a notice indicating where to find the&#xA;  applicable terms.&#xA;&#xA;  Additional terms, permissive or non-permissive, may be&#xA;  stated in the form of a separately written license, or&#xA;  stated as exceptions; the above requirements apply either&#xA;  way.&#xA;&#xA;  8. Termination.&#xA;&#xA;  You may not propagate or modify a covered work except as&#xA;  expressly provided under this License.  Any attempt&#xA;  otherwise to propagate or modify it is void, and will&#xA;  automatically terminate your rights under this License (&#xA;  including any patent licenses granted under the third&#xA;  paragraph of section 11).&#xA;&#xA;  However, if you cease all violation of this License, then&#xA;  your license from a particular copyright holder is&#xA;  reinstated (a) provisionally, unless and until the&#xA;  copyright holder explicitly and finally terminates your&#xA;  license, and (b) permanently, if the copyright holder&#xA;  fails to notify you of the violation by some reasonable&#xA;  means prior to 60 days after the cessation.&#xA;&#xA;  Moreover, your license from a particular copyright holder&#xA;  is reinstated permanently if the copyright holder&#xA;  notifies you of the violation by some reasonable means,&#xA;  this is the first time you have received notice of&#xA;  violation of this License (for any work) from that&#xA;  copyright holder, and you cure the violation prior to 30&#xA;  days after your receipt of the notice.&#xA;&#xA;  Termination of your rights under this section does not&#xA;  terminate the licenses of parties who have received&#xA;  copies or rights from you under this License.  If your&#xA;  rights have been terminated and not permanently&#xA;  reinstated, you do not qualify to receive new licenses&#xA;  for the same material under section 10.&#xA;&#xA;  9. Acceptance Not Required for Having Copies.&#xA;&#xA;  You are not required to accept this License in order to&#xA;  receive or run a copy of the Program.  Ancillary&#xA;  propagation of a covered work occurring solely as a&#xA;  consequence of using peer-to-peer transmission to receive&#xA;  a copy likewise does not require acceptance.  However,&#xA;  nothing other than this License grants you permission to&#xA;  propagate or modify any covered work.  These actions&#xA;  infringe copyright if you do not accept this License.&#xA;  Therefore, by modifying or propagating a covered work,&#xA;  you indicate your acceptance of this License to do so.&#xA;&#xA;  10. Automatic Licensing of Downstream Recipients.&#xA;&#xA;  Each time you convey a covered work, the recipient&#xA;  automatically receives a license from the original&#xA;  licensors, to run, modify and propagate that work,&#xA;  subject to this License.  You are not responsible for&#xA;  enforcing compliance by third parties with this License.&#xA;&#xA;  An &quot;entity transaction&quot; is a transaction transferring&#xA;  control of an organization, or substantially all assets&#xA;  of one, or subdividing an organization, or merging&#xA;  organizations.  If propagation of a covered work results&#xA;  from an entity transaction, each party to that&#xA;  transaction who receives a copy of the work also receives&#xA;  whatever licenses to the work the party&apos;s predecessor in&#xA;  interest had or could give under the previous paragraph,&#xA;  plus a right to possession of the Corresponding Source of&#xA;  the work from the predecessor in interest, if the&#xA;  predecessor has it or can get it with reasonable efforts.&#xA;&#xA;  You may not impose any further restrictions on the&#xA;  exercise of the rights granted or affirmed under this&#xA;  License.  For example, you may not impose a license fee,&#xA;  royalty, or other charge for exercise of rights granted&#xA;  under this License, and you may not initiate litigation (&#xA;  including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit)&#xA;  alleging that any patent claim is infringed by making,&#xA;  using, selling, offering for sale, or importing the&#xA;  Program or any portion of it.&#xA;&#xA;  11. Patents.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;contributor&quot; is a copyright holder who authorizes use&#xA;  under this License of the Program or a work on which the&#xA;  Program is based.  The work thus licensed is called the&#xA;  contributor&apos;s &quot;contributor version&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;  A contributor&apos;s &quot;essential patent claims&quot; are all patent&#xA;  claims owned or controlled by the contributor, whether&#xA;  already acquired or hereafter acquired, that would be&#xA;  infringed by some manner, permitted by this License, of&#xA;  making, using, or selling its contributor version, but do&#xA;  not include claims that would be infringed only as a&#xA;  consequence of further modification of the contributor&#xA;  version.  For purposes of this definition, &quot;control&quot;&#xA;  includes the right to grant patent sublicenses in a&#xA;  manner consistent with the requirements of this License.&#xA;&#xA;  Each contributor grants you a non-exclusive, worldwide,&#xA;  royalty-free patent license under the contributor&apos;s&#xA;  essential patent claims, to make, use, sell, offer for&#xA;  sale, import and otherwise run, modify and propagate the&#xA;  contents of its contributor version.&#xA;&#xA;  In the following three paragraphs, a &quot;patent license&quot; is&#xA;  any express agreement or commitment, however denominated,&#xA;  not to enforce a patent (such as an express permission to&#xA;  practice a patent or covenant not to sue for patent&#xA;  infringement).  To &quot;grant&quot; such a patent license to a&#xA;  party means to make such an agreement or commitment not&#xA;  to enforce a patent against the party.&#xA;&#xA;  If you convey a covered work, knowingly relying on a&#xA;  patent license, and the Corresponding Source of the work&#xA;  is not available for anyone to copy, free of charge and&#xA;  under the terms of this License, through a publicly&#xA;  available network server or other readily accessible&#xA;  means, then you must either (1) cause the Corresponding&#xA;  Source to be so available, or (2) arrange to deprive&#xA;  yourself of the benefit of the patent license for this&#xA;  particular work, or (3) arrange, in a manner consistent&#xA;  with the requirements of this License, to extend the&#xA;  patent license to downstream recipients.  &quot;Knowingly&#xA;  relying&quot; means you have actual knowledge that, but for&#xA;  the patent license, your conveying the covered work in a&#xA;  country, or your recipient&apos;s use of the covered work in a&#xA;  country, would infringe one or more identifiable patents&#xA;  in that country that you have reason to believe are valid.&#xA;&#xA;  If, pursuant to or in connection with a single&#xA;  transaction or arrangement, you convey, or propagate by&#xA;  procuring conveyance of, a covered work, and grant a&#xA;  patent license to some of the parties receiving the&#xA;  covered work authorizing them to use, propagate, modify&#xA;  or convey a specific copy of the covered work, then the&#xA;  patent license you grant is automatically extended to all&#xA;  recipients of the covered work and works based on it.&#xA;&#xA;  A patent license is &quot;discriminatory&quot; if it does not&#xA;  include within the scope of its coverage, prohibits the&#xA;  exercise of, or is conditioned on the non-exercise of one&#xA;  or more of the rights that are specifically granted under&#xA;  this License.  You may not convey a covered work if you&#xA;  are a party to an arrangement with a third party that is&#xA;  in the business of distributing software, under which you&#xA;  make payment to the third party based on the extent of&#xA;  your activity of conveying the work, and under which the&#xA;  third party grants, to any of the parties who would&#xA;  receive the covered work from you, a discriminatory&#xA;  patent license (a) in connection with copies of the&#xA;  covered work conveyed by you (or copies made from those&#xA;  copies), or (b) primarily for and in connection with&#xA;  specific products or compilations that contain the&#xA;  covered work, unless you entered into that arrangement,&#xA;  or that patent license was granted, prior to 28 March&#xA;  2007.&#xA;&#xA;  Nothing in this License shall be construed as excluding&#xA;  or limiting any implied license or other defenses to&#xA;  infringement that may otherwise be available to you under&#xA;  applicable patent law.&#xA;&#xA;  12. No Surrender of Others&apos; Freedom.&#xA;&#xA;  If conditions are imposed on you (whether by court order,&#xA;  agreement or otherwise) that contradict the conditions of&#xA;  this License, they do not excuse you from the conditions&#xA;  of this License.  If you cannot convey a covered work so&#xA;  as to satisfy simultaneously your obligations under this&#xA;  License and any other pertinent obligations, then as a&#xA;  consequence you may not convey it at all.  For example,&#xA;  if you agree to terms that obligate you to collect a&#xA;  royalty for further conveying from those to whom you&#xA;  convey the Program, the only way you could satisfy both&#xA;  those terms and this License would be to refrain entirely&#xA;  from conveying the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  13. Use with the GNU Affero General Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  Notwithstanding any other provision of this License, you&#xA;  have permission to link or combine any covered work with&#xA;  a work licensed under version 3 of the GNU Affero General&#xA;  Public License into a single combined work, and to convey&#xA;  the resulting work.  The terms of this License will&#xA;  continue to apply to the part which is the covered work,&#xA;  but the special requirements of the GNU Affero General&#xA;  Public License, section 13, concerning interaction&#xA;  through a network will apply to the combination as such.&#xA;&#xA;  14. Revised Versions of this License.&#xA;&#xA;  The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or&#xA;  new versions of the GNU General Public License from time&#xA;  to time.  Such new versions will be similar in spirit to&#xA;  the present version, but may differ in detail to address&#xA;  new problems or concerns.&#xA;&#xA;  Each version is given a distinguishing version number.&#xA;  If the Program specifies that a certain numbered version&#xA;  of the GNU General Public License &quot;or any later version&quot;&#xA;  applies to it, you have the option of following the terms&#xA;  and conditions either of that numbered version or of any&#xA;  later version published by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;  If the Program does not specify a version number of the&#xA;  GNU General Public License, you may choose any version&#xA;  ever published by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;&#xA;  If the Program specifies that a proxy can decide which&#xA;  future versions of the GNU General Public License can be&#xA;  used, that proxy&apos;s public statement of acceptance of a&#xA;  version permanently authorizes you to choose that version&#xA;  for the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  Later license versions may give you additional or&#xA;  different permissions.  However, no additional&#xA;  obligations are imposed on any author or copyright holder&#xA;  as a result of your choosing to follow a later version.&#xA;&#xA;  15. Disclaimer of Warranty.&#xA;&#xA;  THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE PROGRAM, TO THE EXTENT&#xA;  PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.  EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE&#xA;  STATED IN WRITING THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER&#xA;  PARTIES PROVIDE THE PROGRAM &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF&#xA;  ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT&#xA;  LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND&#xA;  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO&#xA;  THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE PROGRAM IS WITH YOU.&#xA;  SHOULD THE PROGRAM PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE COST&#xA;  OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.&#xA;&#xA;  16. Limitation of Liability.&#xA;&#xA;  IN NO EVENT UNLESS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW OR AGREED&#xA;  TO IN WRITING WILL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER&#xA;  PARTY WHO MODIFIES AND/OR CONVEYS THE PROGRAM AS&#xA;  PERMITTED ABOVE, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES, INCLUDING&#xA;  ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES&#xA;  ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE PROGRAM (&#xA;  INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING&#xA;  RENDERED INACCURATE OR LOSSES SUSTAINED BY YOU OR THIRD&#xA;  PARTIES OR A FAILURE OF THE PROGRAM TO OPERATE WITH ANY&#xA;  OTHER PROGRAMS), EVEN IF SUCH HOLDER OR OTHER PARTY HAS&#xA;  BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;  17. Interpretation of Sections 15 and 16.&#xA;&#xA;  If the disclaimer of warranty and limitation of liability&#xA;  provided above cannot be given local legal effect&#xA;  according to their terms, reviewing courts shall apply&#xA;  local law that most closely approximates an absolute&#xA;  waiver of all civil liability in connection with the&#xA;  Program, unless a warranty or assumption of liability&#xA;  accompanies a copy of the Program in return for a fee.&#xA;  &#xA;       GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE&#xA;                       Version 3, 29 June 2007&#xA;&#xA; Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. &lt;http://&#xA; fsf.org/&gt; Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute&#xA; verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it&#xA; is not allowed.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;  This version of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  incorporates the terms and conditions of version 3 of the&#xA;  GNU General Public License, supplemented by the&#xA;  additional permissions listed below.&#xA;&#xA;  0. Additional Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;  As used herein, &quot;this License&quot; refers to version 3 of the&#xA;  GNU Lesser General Public License, and the &quot;GNU GPL&quot;&#xA;  refers to version 3 of the GNU General Public License.&#xA;&#xA;  &quot;The Library&quot; refers to a covered work governed by this&#xA;  License, other than an Application or a Combined Work as&#xA;  defined below.&#xA;&#xA;  An &quot;Application&quot; is any work that makes use of an&#xA;  interface provided by the Library, but which is not&#xA;  otherwise based on the Library. Defining a subclass of a&#xA;  class defined by the Library is deemed a mode of using an&#xA;  interface provided by the Library.&#xA;&#xA;  A &quot;Combined Work&quot; is a work produced by combining or&#xA;  linking an Application with the Library.  The particular&#xA;  version of the Library with which the Combined Work was&#xA;  made is also called the &quot;Linked Version&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Minimal Corresponding Source&quot; for a Combined Work&#xA;  means the Corresponding Source for the Combined Work,&#xA;  excluding any source code for portions of the Combined&#xA;  Work that, considered in isolation, are based on the&#xA;  Application, and not on the Linked Version.&#xA;&#xA;  The &quot;Corresponding Application Code&quot; for a Combined Work&#xA;  means the object code and/or source code for the&#xA;  Application, including any data and utility programs&#xA;  needed for reproducing the Combined Work from the&#xA;  Application, but excluding the System Libraries of the&#xA;  Combined Work.&#xA;&#xA;  1. Exception to Section 3 of the GNU GPL.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a covered work under sections 3 and 4 of&#xA;  this License without being bound by section 3 of the GNU&#xA;  GPL.&#xA;&#xA;  2. Conveying Modified Versions.&#xA;&#xA;  If you modify a copy of the Library, and, in your&#xA;  modifications, a facility refers to a function or data to&#xA;  be supplied by an Application that uses the facility (&#xA;  other than as an argument passed when the facility is&#xA;  invoked), then you may convey a copy of the modified&#xA;  version:&#xA;&#xA;   a) under this License, provided that you make a good&#xA;   faith effort to ensure that, in the event an Application&#xA;   does not supply the function or data, the facility still&#xA;   operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose&#xA;   remains meaningful, or&#xA;&#xA;   b) under the GNU GPL, with none of the additional&#xA;   permissions of this License applicable to that copy.&#xA;&#xA;  3. Object Code Incorporating Material from Library Header&#xA;  Files.&#xA;&#xA;  The object code form of an Application may incorporate&#xA;  material from a header file that is part of the Library.&#xA;  You may convey such object code under terms of your&#xA;  choice, provided that, if the incorporated material is&#xA;  not limited to numerical parameters, data structure&#xA;  layouts and accessors, or small macros, inline functions&#xA;  and templates (ten or fewer lines in length), you do both&#xA;  of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the object&#xA;   code that the Library is used in it and that the Library&#xA;   and its use are covered by this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Accompany the object code with a copy of the GNU GPL&#xA;   and this license document.&#xA;&#xA;  4. Combined Works.&#xA;&#xA;  You may convey a Combined Work under terms of your choice&#xA;  that, taken together, effectively do not restrict&#xA;  modification of the portions of the Library contained in&#xA;  the Combined Work and reverse engineering for debugging&#xA;  such modifications, if you also do each of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the Combined&#xA;   Work that the Library is used in it and that the Library&#xA;   and its use are covered by this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Accompany the Combined Work with a copy of the GNU&#xA;   GPL and this license document.&#xA;&#xA;   c) For a Combined Work that displays copyright notices&#xA;   during execution, include the copyright notice for the&#xA;   Library among these notices, as well as a reference&#xA;   directing the user to the copies of the GNU GPL and this&#xA;   license document.&#xA;&#xA;   d) Do one of the following:&#xA;&#xA;       0) Convey the Minimal Corresponding Source under the&#xA;       terms of this License, and the Corresponding&#xA;       Application Code in a form suitable for, and under&#xA;       terms that permit, the user to recombine or relink&#xA;       the Application with a modified version of the&#xA;       Linked Version to produce a modified Combined Work,&#xA;       in the manner specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL&#xA;       for conveying Corresponding Source.&#xA;&#xA;       1) Use a suitable shared library mechanism for&#xA;       linking with the Library.  A suitable mechanism is&#xA;       one that (a) uses at run time a copy of the Library&#xA;       already present on the user&apos;s computer system, and (&#xA;       b) will operate properly with a modified version of&#xA;       the Library that is interface-compatible with the&#xA;       Linked Version.&#xA;&#xA;   e) Provide Installation Information, but only if you&#xA;   would otherwise be required to provide such information&#xA;   under section 6 of the GNU GPL, and only to the extent&#xA;   that such information is necessary to install and&#xA;   execute a modified version of the Combined Work produced&#xA;   by recombining or relinking the Application with a&#xA;   modified version of the Linked Version. (If you use&#xA;   option 4d0, the Installation Information must accompany&#xA;   the Minimal Corresponding Source and Corresponding&#xA;   Application Code. If you use option 4d1, you must&#xA;   provide the Installation Information in the manner&#xA;   specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL for conveying&#xA;   Corresponding Source.)&#xA;&#xA;  5. Combined Libraries.&#xA;&#xA;  You may place library facilities that are a work based on&#xA;  the Library side by side in a single library together&#xA;  with other library facilities that are not Applications&#xA;  and are not covered by this License, and convey such a&#xA;  combined library under terms of your choice, if you do&#xA;  both of the following:&#xA;&#xA;   a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the&#xA;   same work based on the Library, uncombined with any&#xA;   other library facilities, conveyed under the terms of&#xA;   this License.&#xA;&#xA;   b) Give prominent notice with the combined library that&#xA;   part of it is a work based on the Library, and&#xA;   explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined&#xA;   form of the same work.&#xA;&#xA;  6. Revised Versions of the GNU Lesser General Public&#xA;  License.&#xA;&#xA;  The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or&#xA;  new versions of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in&#xA;  spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail&#xA;  to address new problems or concerns.&#xA;&#xA;  Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If&#xA;  the Library as you received it specifies that a certain&#xA;  numbered version of the GNU Lesser General Public License&#xA;  &quot;or any later version&quot; applies to it, you have the option&#xA;  of following the terms and conditions either of that&#xA;  published version or of any later version published by&#xA;  the Free Software Foundation. If the Library as you&#xA;  received it does not specify a version number of the GNU&#xA;  Lesser General Public License, you may choose any version&#xA;  of the GNU Lesser General Public License ever published&#xA;  by the Free Software Foundation.&#xA;&#xA;  If the Library as you received it specifies that a proxy&#xA;  can decide whether future versions of the GNU Lesser&#xA;  General Public License shall apply, that proxy&apos;s public&#xA;  statement of acceptance of any version is permanent&#xA;  authorization for you to choose that version for the&#xA;  Library.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2004-2008 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.FreeMem' version='1.0.0.25-cMQhvE'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='FreeMem (Eclipse 2.x and 3.x)'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.FreeMem' version='1.0.0.25-cMQhvE'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.FreeMemFeature.feature.group' range='[1.3.0,1.3.0]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' version='1.2.5'>
      <properties size='3'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='RssViewFeature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='RSS View is an RSS/Atom reader that keeps you always up-to-date. Unlike standard news readers, it is designed to integrate into Eclipse. Thus, you have everything at one place. RSS View may even improve your development process by integrating your bug tracker, development forum or wiki directly in your IDE.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.jar' version='1.2.5'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature' version='1.2.5'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature' version='1.2.5'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;&#xA;You are free:&#xA;&#xA;    * to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;    * to make commercial use of the work&#xA;&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon this work.&#xA;&#xA;    * For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others the license terms of this work.&#xA;    * Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission from the copyright holder.&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2007 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.RSS_View' version='1.0.0.47C79cMRTvE'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='RSS View (Eclipse 3.x)'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='http://junginger.biz/eclipse/site.xml.RSS_View' version='1.0.0.47C79cMRTvE'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' range='[1.5.0,1.5.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.RssViewFeature.feature.group' range='[1.2.5,1.2.5]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.0'>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='ExploreFS Feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='Open the folder of any selected item directly in Windows Explorer'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.junginger.biz/eclipse/'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='www.junginger.biz'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='biz.junginger.ExploreFS_Feature' version='1.0.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/' url='http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/'>
          Creative Commons License, Attribution-NoDerivs 2.0&#xA;You are free:&#xA;* to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work&#xA;* to make commercial use of the work&#xA;Under the following conditions:&#xA;By Attribution. You must give the original author credit.&#xA;No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon&#xA;this work.&#xA;* For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others&#xA;the license terms of this work.&#xA;* Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission&#xA;from the copyright holder.&#xA;More information: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        (C) Copyright 2007 Markus Oliver Junginger. All rights reserved.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
